Guide to the Frank H. T. Rhodes papers,1977-1996.
Rhodes, Frank H. T. papers, 1977-1996.
- Series XIX. Speeches
  - Br. Remarks -Presidents' Day Luncheon, 21 Feb 94 (Box 343, Folder 61)
  - Br. Remarks - Q& A - Alan & Betsy Harris Luncheon, 25 Feb 94 (Box 343, Folder 62)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Rhodes/Marshall Scholarship Dinner, 02 Mar 94 (Box 343, Folder 63)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Class of '59 Video, 07 Mar 94 (Box 343, Folder 64)
  - Br. Remarks/Q& A - Parents VIP Campus Visit, 11 Mar 94 (Box 343, Folder 65)
  - Br. Remarks - Anne Gibbons Recognition, 16 Mar 94 (Box 343, Folder 66)
  - Br. Remarks - Ron & Susan Lynch Recognition, 17 Mar 94 (Box 343, Folder 67)
  - Keynote Speech - Vet College Centennial Luncheon, 21 Mar 94 (Box 343, Folder 68)
  - Give Toast - Vet College Centennial Dinner, 21 Mar 94 (Box 343, Folder 69)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Legislative Reception in Albany, 22 Mar 94 (Box 343, Folder 70)
  - Introduction - Bartels' Lecturer - Sir John Burgh, 29 Mar 94 (Box 343, Folder 71)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Honoring Professor Tigner as Bethe Chair, 30 Mar 94 (Box 343, Folder 72)
  - Br. Remarks/Q& A - International Living Center, 05 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 73)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Video for Administrative Management Institute, 05 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 74)
  - Br. Remarks/Present Award - Entrepreneur & Personal Enterprise-Dr. Irwin Jacobs, 07 APR 94 (Box 343, Folder 75)
  - Br. Remarks/Q& A - Engineering VIP Campus Visit, 08 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 76)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Buick Volunteer Service Awards, 08 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 77)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Management Policy Council Dinner, 13 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 78)
  - Opening Remarks/Q& A - Academic Leadership Forum, 15 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 79)
  - Closing Remarks - Academic Leadership Forum, 15 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 80)
  - Br. Remarks - Hotel Ezra Cornell, 16 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 81)
  - Br. Remarks - Law School Advisory Council, 23 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 82)
  - Br. Remarks - Washington Regional Campaign Kick-off, 27 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 83)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Bronfenbrenner Tribute, 27 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 84)
  - Br. Remarks - Baltimore Regional Campaign Kick-off, 28 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 85)
  - Br. Remarks - Faculty-in-Residence/Faculty Fellows Reception, 28 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 86)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Assemblies Thank-you, 29 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 87)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Milstein Recognition Dinner, 29 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 88)
  - Br. Remarks - Dedication of Reis Tennis Center, 30 Apr 94 (Box 343, Folder 89)
  - V. Br. Remarks - International Student Reception, 03 May 94 (Box 343, Folder 90)
  - Toast/V. Br. Remarks - Bob Wilson's Birthday, 07 May 94 (Box 343, Folder 91)
  - Br. Remarks - Ferris Family Professorship, 09 May 94 (Box 343, Folder 92)
  - Br. Remarks - Dedication of Robinson Professorship, 10 May 94 (Box 343, Folder 93)
  - Br. Remarks - Academic Leadership Series, 10 May 94 (Box 343, Folder 94)
  - Br. Remarks - CALS Faculty Convocation, 12 May 94 (Box 343, Folder 95)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Dinner for Dennis O'Brien w/Area Presidents, 13 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 01)
  - Br. Remarks - Albany Regional Campaign Kick-off, 17 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 02)
  - Br. Remarks - Major Gifts Committee Meeting, 18 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 03)
  - Remarks - NYC Tower Club Dinner, 18 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 04)
  - V. Br. Remarks - L. Pearce Williams Recognition, 19 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 05)
  - Speech - Canisius College Commencement, 21 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 06)
  - Speech - Law School Convocation, 22 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 07)
  - Br. Remarks/Present Certificates - Merrill Presidential Scholars, 24 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 08)
  - Sam Johnson -Lindenberg Award, 25 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 09)
  - Speech - CUMC Commencement, 26 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 10)
  - Br. Remarks - Senior Class Trustee Reception, 28 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 11)
  - Br. Remarks - Doctoral Recognition Ceremony, 28 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 12)
  - Remarks - Trustee Dinner Honoring Dale Corson, 28 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 13)
  - Br. Remarks/Introduce - Baccalaureate Speaker - Dennis O'Brien, 29 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 14)
  - Speech - Commencement - "Is There Life After Cornell?", 29 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 15)
  - Remarks - Council on Competitiveness, 31 May 94 (Box 344, Folder 16)
  - Br. Remarks - Employee Service Recognition Banquet, 01 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 17)
  - Br. Remarks/Welcome - NYS Science & Technology Foundation, 06 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 18)
  - Br. Remarks - Plantations' Sponsors Luncheon, 09 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 19)
  - Br. Remarks - Kiplinger Professorship Dedication, 09 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 20)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Class of '44 - 50th Reunion Dinner, 09 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 21)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Class of '59 Brunch, 10 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 22)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Plantations Path Inauguration Celebration, 10 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 23)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Reunion Recognition Breakfast, 10 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 24)
  - Introduce - Olin Lecturer - Martin Fettman, 10 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 25)
  - Check/Thank-you - Class of '54 Dinner, 10 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 26)
  - Speech - State-of-the-U. - CAA Annual Meeting, 11 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 27)
  - Check/Thank-you - Class of '74 Luncheon, 11 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 28)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Sprecher Luncheon, 11 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 29)
  - Check/Br. Remarks - Class of '69 - 25th Reunion Dinner, 11 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 30)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Cornelliana Night, 11 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 31)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Plantations Path Community Opening, 14 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 32)
  - Br. Remarks - Carl Kroch/Chuck Lake Birthday Dinner, 17 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 33)
  - V. Br. Remarks - End-of-the-Year Bash, 20 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 34)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Reception for Larry Palmer, 21 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 35)
  - Br. Remarks - Trustee Dinner, 22 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 36)
  - V. Br. Remarks - ILR-Cooperative Extension Ribbon Cutting - NYC, 23 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 37)
  - Br. Remarks - New Trustee Orientation, 23 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 38)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Reception for Stuart Lynn, 24 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 39)
  - V. Br. Remarks - NYS Science & Technology Foundation Board Meeting, 28 June 94 (Box 344, Folder 40)
  - V. Br. Remarks - University of Stirling Honorary Degree, 01 July 94 (Box 344, Folder 41)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Alumni in Turkey, 13 Aug 94 (Box 344, Folder 42)
  - Br. Remarks - Convocation for New Students - "Welcome to Cornell", 20 Aug 94 (Box 344, Folder 43)
  - Br. Remarks - CUMC Opening Exercises, 24 Aug 94 (Box 344, Folder 44)
  - Greeting - Sage Chapel Opening Service, 28 Aug 94 (Box 344, Folder 45)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Meet with Coaches and Football Team, 29 Aug 94 (Box 344, Folder 46)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Reception for Laing Kennedy, 29 Aug 94 (Box 344, Folder 47)
  - Br. Remarks - Assemblies Retreat, 30 Aug 94 (Box 344, Folder 48)
  - Introductory Remarks - Meeting with University Chaplains, 01 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 49)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Chemistry Department Luncheon, 01 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 50)
  - Br. Remarks - Library Campus VIP Visit Dinner, 09 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 51)
  - Br. Remarks - 90th Anniversary CU in Rochester, 12 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 52)
  - Br. Remarks - Culpepper Foundation Dinner, 13 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 53)
  - Br. Remarks - McKelvey Recognition, 14 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 54)
  - Br. Remarks - Dedication of Weiss Family Lounge, 17 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 55)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Half-time Interview - CU/Princeton Game, 17 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 56)
  - Br. Remarks - Arthur Wiesenberger Luncheon, 21 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 57)
  - Br. Remarks - Snee Video, 22 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 58)
  - Br. Remarks - Meakem Recognition Dinner, 23 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 59)
  - Br. Remarks - QIP Instructors Luncheon, 23 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 60)
  - Wedding Toast - Anne Gibbons Wedding, 24 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 61)
  - Remarks - Council on Competitiveness, 26 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 62)
  - V. Br. Remarks - New Faculty Orientation Reception, 27 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 63)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Campus VIP Visit - Music, 30 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 64)
  - Speech - Inauguration of Fr. Harold Ridley - Loyola College, 30 Sept 94 (Box 344, Folder 65)
  - Br. Remarks - Community Leaders' Brunch, 01 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 66)
  - Br. Remarks - Cornell University Financial Forum, 03 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 67)
  - V. Br. Remarks - New Faculty Orientation Reception, 03 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 68)
  - Br. Remarks - Les Severinghaus Memorial Service, 03 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 69)
  - Br. Remarks - Dyson Charitable Fund Board Meeting, 11 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 70)
  - Speech - State-of-the-U. - FCR, 12 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 71)
  - Remarks - Carl Sagan Birthday Dinner, 14 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 72)
  - Br. Remarks - Pittsburgh Campaign Kick-off, 18 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 73)
  - Introduction - Janet Reno Presentation, 20 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 74)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Alumni Affairs/Development Committee Breakfast, 21 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 75)
  - Speech - State-of-the-U. - Trustee/Council Weekend, 21 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 76)
  - V. Br. Remarks - New Faculty Orientation Reception, 24 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 77)
  - Br. Remarks - COFHE Fall Assembly, 24 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 78)
  - V. Br. Remarks - New Faculty Orientation Reception [empty], 25 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 78)
  - Introduce - Neal Lane - NSF, 25 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 79)
  - Speech - Academic Leadership Series, 28 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 80)
  - Introduce - Paul Tregurtha - Academic Leadership Series, 28 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 81)
  - Br. Remarks - Tom & Nancy Clark Recognition Dinner, 28 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 82)
  - Br. Remarks - Atlanta Campaign Kick-off, 29 Oct 94 (Box 344, Folder 83)
  - Br. Remarks - Detroit Campaign Kick-off, 02 Nov 94 (Box 344, Folder 84)
  - Introductory Remarks - Hatfield Fellow - James Houghton, 03 Nov 94 (Box 344, Folder 85)
  - Br. Welcome - Family Weekend, 05 Nov 94 (Box 344, Folder 86)
  - Br. Remarks - Milwaukee Campaign Kick-off, 09 Nov 94 (Box 344, Folder 87)
  - Br. Remarks - Kansas City Campaign Kick-off, 10 Nov 94 (Box 344, Folder 88)
  - Br. Remarks - Tulsa Campaign Kick-off, 11 Nov 94 (Box 344, Folder 89)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Bartels' Luncheon for Michael Manley, 15 Nov 94 (Box 344, Folder 90)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Half-time Interview-CU/Penn Game, 19 Nov 94 (Box 344, Folder 91)
  - Br. Remarks - Puerto Rico Campaign Dinner, 02 Dec 94 (Box 344, Folder 92)
  - Read Scripture - Sage Chapel Christmas Program, 04 Dec 94 (Box 344, Folder 93)
  - Br. Remarks - Ithaca/Syracuse/Binghamton Celebration, 05 December 1994 (Box 344, Folder 94)
  - Br. Remarks - Ithaca Video Introduction, 05 Dec 94 (Box 344, Folder 95)
  - Br. Welcome - Hunter Rawlings Visit, 11 Dec 94 (Box 344, Folder 96)
  - Br. Remarks - Syracuse MDA Annual Meeting - done by JEM, 15 Dec 94 (Box 344, Folder 97)
  - Br. Remarks - January Graduates Reception - done by MCN, 16 December 1994 (Box 344, Folder 98)
  - Video Remarks - Weiss, Peck & Greer Anniversary, 16 Jan 95 (Box 344, Folder 99)
  - Br. Remarks - International Students Reception, 16 Jan 95 (Box 344, Folder 100)
  - Br. Remarks - Cabaret, 23 Jan 95 (Box 344, Folder 101)
  - Br. Remarks - President's Circle Dinner, 25 Jan 95 (Box 345, Folder 01)
  - Br. Remarks - Strategic Planning Presentation [empty], 27 Jan 95 (Box 345, Folder 02)
  - Remarks - Cornell Assoc. of Class Officers (CACO) Midwinter Meeting, 28 January 1995 (Box 345, Folder 03)
  - Opening Remarks - Council on Competitiveness, 31 Jan 95 (Box 345, Folder 04)
  - Br. Introduction - Robert Walker and George Brown to NSB, 31 Jan 95 (Box 345, Folder 05)
  - Speech - MIT Symposium - "Science in the National Interest", 07 Feb 95 (Box 345, Folder 06-8)
  - Br. Remarks - Tampa Kick-off Celebration, 13 Feb 95 (Box 345, Folder 09)
  - Br. Remarks - Sarasota Kick-off Celebration, 15 Feb 95 (Box 345, Folder 10)
  - Br. Remarks - Alan Harris Luncheon, 16 Feb 95 (Box 345, Folder 11)
  - Investment Committee Jokes, 17 Feb 95 (Box 345, Folder 12)
  - Br. Remarks - Palm Beach Kick-off Celebration, 20 Feb 95 (Box 345, Folder 13)
  - Br. Remarks - Ft. Lauderdale Kick-off Celebration, 23 February 1995 (Box 345, Folder 14)
  - Br. Remarks - Miami Kick-off Celebration, 24 Feb 95 (Box 345, Folder 15)
  - V. Br. Remarks - John Wiesenfeld Reception, 28 Feb 95 (Box 345, Folder 16)
  - Br. Remarks - New Faculty Orientation, 01 Mar 95 (Box 345, Folder 17)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Introduce Messenger Lecturer - Ross Chambers, 06 Mar 95 (Box 345, Folder 18)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Faculty Fellows/Faculty-in-Residence Reception, 15 Mar 95 (Box 345, Folder 19)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Tessler Recognition Dinner, 15 Mar 95 (Box 345, Folder 20)
  - Br. Remarks - Schaenen/Stewart Trustee Dinner, 16 Mar 95 (Box 345, Folder 21)
  - V. Br. Remarks - GTE Gift Presentation, 17 March 1995 (Box 345, Folder 22)
  - Br. Remarks - Dean Phemister Dinner, 18 Mar 95 (Box 345, Folder 23)
  - Br. Remarks - Hartford Campaign Celebration, 28 Mar 95 (Box 345, Folder 24)
  - Br. Remarks/Presentation - Entrepreneur-of-the-Year Dinner, 30 Mar 95 (Box 345, Folder 25)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Museum Campus Visit, 31 Mar 95 (Box 345, Folder 26)
  - Br. Remarks - Bethe Symposium; Br. Remarks/Present Citation - Bethe Dinner, 01 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 27)
  - Br. Remarks - Japan Alumni Dinner - Tokyo, 04 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 28)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Ambassador Laney Dinner - Seoul, 05 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 29)
  - Br. Remarks - Korean Alumni Dinner - Seoul, 06 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 29)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Tang/Miller/Tien/Burns Dinner - Hong Kong, 07 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 30)
  - Br. Remarks - Hong Kong Alumni Dinner, 08 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 30)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Michael Tien Dinner - Hong Kong, 09 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 30)
  - V. Br. Remarks - L. T. Lam Champagne Reception - Hong Kong, 09 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 30)
  - Br. Remarks - Taipei Alumni Dinner - Taiwan, 10 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 31)
  - V. Br. Remarks - President Lee Dinner - Taiwan, 11 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 31)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Academica Sinca Dinner, 11 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 32)
  - Br. Remarks - Honorary Degree Ceremony - University of Sydney, 13 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 33)
  - Br. Remarks - Dinner Honoring Malden Nesheim, 19 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 34)
  - Br. Remarks - Trustee Dinner Honoring Malden Nesheim, 20 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 35)
  - Br. Remarks - New Faculty Orientation, 27 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 36)
  - Br. Remarks - Tompkins County Area Development Group, 28 April 95 (Box 345, Folder 37)
  - Br. Remarks - Undergraduate Research Forum, 28 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 38)
  - Br. Remarks - Parents' Campus Visit, 28 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 39)
  - Br. Remarks - PCCW Dinner, 29 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 40)
  - Br. Remarks - Engineering College Advisory Council, 29 Apr 95 (Box 345, Folder 41)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Farewell Reception for Dean Call, May 1, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 42)
  - V. Br. Remarks - International Students' Reception, May 2, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 43)
  - V. Br. Remarks - David Starr Jordan Prize Ceremony, May 3, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 44)
  - V. Br. Remarks/Present Statue - Treman Luncheon, May 3, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 45)
  - Br. Remarks/Award Presentation - Perkins' Prize Ceremony, May 4, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 46)
  - Testify - Rome Lab, May 5, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 47)
  - Br. Remarks - Annual Rowing Banquet, May 6, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 48)
  - Br. Remarks - Federation Weekend Leadership Banquet, May 6, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 49)
  - Remarks - Academic Leadership Series, May 8, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 50)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Boy Scout Distinguished Citizenship Award, May 9, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 51)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Parade Thank-you (not given), May 9, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 52)
  - Speech - UCLA General Education Symposium, May 15, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 53)
  - Br. Remarks - CUMC Board of Overseers - Farewell, May 17, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 54)
  - Br. Remarks - Harold Tanner Dinner, May 18, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 55)
  - Br. Remarks - Major Gifts Committee Meeting, May 19, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 56)
  - Br. Remarks - New York Tower Club Dinner, May 19, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 57)
  - Br. Remarks - Trustee Dinner Honoring Malden Nesheim, May 20, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 58)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Ithaca College Commencement, May 21, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 59)
  - Speech - Law School Convocation, May 21, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 60)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Symposium Honoring FHTR, May 21, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 61)
  - Br. Remarks - Merrill Scholars Luncheon, May 23, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 62)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Retiring Faculty Reception, May 24, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 63)
  - Speech - Cornell University Medical College Commencement, May 25, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 64)
  - Br. Remarks - Senior Class Trustee Reception, May 26, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 65)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Alumni Affairs and Development Committee Meeting, May 27, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 66)
  - Br. Remarks - Ph.D. Ceremony, May 27, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 67)
  - Br. Remarks - Trustee Dinner, May 27, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 68)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Introduce Baccalaureate Speaker, May 28, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 69)
  - Speech - Commencement - "From Ithaca to Ithaca", May 28, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 70)
  - Br. Remarks - Employee Service Recognition Banquet, June 1, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 71)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Class of '45-50th Reunion Dinner, June 8, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 72)
  - Br. Welcome - Introduce Lee Teng-hui - Ag Quad Reception, June 8, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 73)
  - Br. Remarks - Reunion Recognition Breakfast, June 9, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 74)
  - Br. Remarks - Central Ave. Dedication - Ho Recognition, June 9, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 75)
  - Br. Remarks - Ho Luncheon, June 9, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 76)
  - Introductory Remarks - Olin Lecturer - Lee Teng-hui, June 9, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 77)
  - Welcome & Toast - Lee Dinner at Home, June 9, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 78)
  - Accept Check/Thanks - Class of '50 Luncheon, June 10, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 79)
  - Accept Check/Thanks - Class of '55 Reception, June 10, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 80)
  - Speech - State-of-the-Univeristy - CAA Annual Meeting, June 10, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 81)
  - Remarks - Class of '70-25th Reunion Dinner, June 10, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 82)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Cornelliana Night, June 10, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 83)
  - V. Br. Remarks - George & Gloria Peter 50th Anniversary, June 11, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 84)
  - Read Scripture - Sage Chapel [empty], June 11, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 84)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Zamorano Board of Trustees, June 15, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 85)
  - Br. Remarks - Memorial Service for Dick Ramin, June 18, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 86)
  - Br. Remarks - End-of-the-Year Bash, June 20, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 87)
  - V. Br. Remarks - Jay Morley Reception, June 23, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 88)
  - Br. Remarks - Cornell Club of London, June 30, 1995 (Box 345, Folder 89)
- Dalai Lama Records, 1991 (Box 346-348)
  Correspondence, background materials, photographs, clippings, news releases, and other subject files pertaining to the visit to the Cornell University campus by the Dalai Lama.
- Miscellaneous Reports (Box 349-350)
  Miscellaneous accumulated reports and background reports, Various Dates
- Volume: Alma Mater Studiorum Saecularia Nona, 1988 (Box 351)
- Volume: Bologna Una Universita per L'Europa, 1988 (Box 351)
- Rhodes's Florida Trip, 1996 (Box 351, Folder 1)
- Rhodes's Reunion Schedule & Briefing, 1996 (Box 351, Folder 2)
- Whitey Mullestein Foremost Benefactor's Ceremony, 1996 (Box 351, Folder 3)
- Leadership Gifts Event - Cape Cod, 1996 (Box 351, Folder 4)
- Responses for the University-Wide Strategic Planning Consultation Draft Presentation Report, 1996 (Box 353, Folder 1-2)
- Administrative Aide manual, 1979-1989 (Box 353, Folder 3)
- 3 VHS tapes (Box 352)